RILEY NEHER

rn50@nyu.edu | 646-706-3456 | New York, New York 10003

C:	1100	m	2	~1	
OI	ш	ши	a	т.	v

Motivated undergraduate student pursuing a degree in Data Science and Mathematics, with 4+ years of experience working in research and the non-profit sector. Recently founded the NYU Chapter of Hack4Impact, an organization devoted to building software for non-profit organizations. Named a Presidential Honors Scholar at New York University, for determined work ethic and strong leadership abilities. Planning to attend NYU London in the Fall.

Skills

- Python / Javascript / R
- MySQL / JSON
- Data Management

- Problem solving
- Data analysis
- Leadership

Experience

Co-Founder, Director | Hack4Impact NYU - New York, New York | 08/2020 - Present

Founded the NYU Chapter of Hack4Impact. Recently worked with the New York City branch of the ACLU to build an interactive data visualization, to broadcast NYPD misconduct data.

Data Analyst Intern | Correctional Association of New York - New York, New York | 05/2020 - 09/2020

Built a web scraper with Selenium and Multiprocessing to track incarcerated individuals during the coronavirus crisis in New York State Prisons. Helped construct a searchable database for the intake letters the organization received.

Research Assistant | Public Safety Lab - New York, New York | 06/2018 - 08/2018

Collected and analyzed data about school calendars by district, in order to match them with respective police precinct data for an ongoing research project.

Research Assistant | BetaGov - New York, New York | 06/2017 - 08/2017

Conducted research and assisted in writing papers for projects involving prison populations and those in need of food stamp assistance.

Relevant Coursework

- Causal Inference, A
- Linear Algebra, A-

- Responsible Data Science, A
- Introduction to Computer Science, A

Education and Training

High School For Math Science And Engineering

New York, NY | 06/2019

High School Diploma

New York University

New York, NY | Expected in 05/2023

Data Science Major, Mathematics Minor